{
  "quiz1": [
    { "question": "Question1", "answer": "Answer1" },
    { "question": "Question2", "answer": "Answer2" }
  ],
  "animals": [
    { "question": "كَلب", "answer": "dog" },
    { "question": "قِط", "answer": "cat" },
    { "question": "أرنب", "answer": "Rabbit" },
    { "question": "دُب", "answer": "Bear" },
    { "question": "فيل", "answer": "Elephant" },
    { "question": "غزالة", "answer": "Deer" },
    { "question": "ثور", "answer": "Bull" },
    { "question": "بقرة", "answer": "Cow" },
    { "question": "ماعز", "answer": "Goat" },
    { "question": "حصان", "answer": "Horse" },
    { "question": "خروف", "answer": "Sheep" }
  ]
}
